(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-02T09:06:27.582927",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
わたし それとも あの娘
Me, or that girl?
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
星を巡るよ 純情
Wandering through the stars, pure emotion.
弱虫 泣き虫 連れて
Bringing along my cowardice and tears,
まだ 行くんだ と 思う わたし
I still think I'll keep going.
愛する より 求める より
Rather than loving, rather than yearning,
疑う 方が ずっと たやすい 自分が悔しい
Suspecting is always easier—I'm frustrated with myself.
痛いよ
It hurts.
味方 だけど 愛してない とか
Being on your side but not loving you,
守る けど 側 に いれ ない とか
Protecting you but not being able to stay by your side—
苦い 二律背反
A bitter contradiction.
今 すぐ タッチ ミー
Touch me right now!
運命 ならば つなげて
If this is destiny, connect us.
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
わたし それとも あの娘
Me, or that girl?
こころ 揺らす 言葉 より
Rather than words that shake my heart,
無責任に 抱いて 限界
Irresponsibly holding me to the limit.
妄想をさばく オキテ
The rules that judge our delusions,
後ろから蹴りあげたら
If you kick them from behind,
むき出しの恋に酔いしれた
I was intoxicated by bare, exposed love.
呼吸だけで精一杯
Just breathing takes all my might.
迎えに来て おぼれてるから
Come rescue me, because I'm drowning.
痛いよ
It hurts.
前向きな嘘 真実に受けるのは
Accepting a positive lie as the truth—
笑ってる声 せめないから
Because your laughing voice doesn't blame me.
未来も手放した
I even let go of the future.
今すぐ hold me 理性なんて押し倒して
Hold me right now, pushing reason aside!
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
わたし それとも あの娘
Me, or that girl?
涙なんて役立たず
Tears are completely useless.
星を駆けるよ 純情
Dash through the stars, pure emotion.
What is the triangler?
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
わたし それとも あの娘
Me, or that girl?
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
わたし それともあの娘?
Me or that girl?
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
星を巡るよ 純情
Go around the stars, pure feelings.
弱虫 泣き虫連れて
Bringing along my coward and crybaby...
まだ行くんだと思う わたし
I thought that I'd still go.
純情
Pure feelings...
緊張して音外しちゃったよ!
Oh, I missed a cue!
大丈夫だよ!
It's fine!
やっちまったよ!
I messed up!
大丈夫だよ!
It's fine, it's fine!
やっちまったよ!
Oh well!
かわいい歌だよ!
It's a cute song!
いい歌だよ!
It's a good song!
みんな盛り上がってるかー?
Everyone having fun?
見に来てくれてありがとう!
Thank you for coming!
今日はかなたとうめで初めての…
Today is Kanata and Watame's...
一緒にライブやっていきたいと思ってさ、みんなでこの…
First time doing a live together!
かなたライブで
Kanata Live!
ツイートとかしてくれたら、こっち、こっち。嬉しいな。
If you could tweet about it, we'd be so happy!
お願いします!お願いしまーす!
Please do!
いや今日結構ね、いっぱい歌うのでね、うん。
We're singing a lot today, so...
頑張ろう!頑張ろう!
Let's do our best!
体力持つかな。そうそう結構ね、はふう…
I might lose my stamina!
大丈夫かなって、ふう。
I think I'll be fine!
息切れと息が頑張りますよ、みんな。ありがとうね。
We'll run out of breath, but let's do our best, everyone!
ありがとう!
Thank you!
えーっと、それでは次いっちゃう?
Alright, should we go to the next one?
もうすぐいっちゃう?
Is it about time?
いっちゃう?
Go?
いっちゃっていいんですか?
Is it really okay?
いっちゃってもよろしいんでしょうか、これ?
Would it be alright if we just went for it?
いいのかな?
Would that be okay?
じゃあいっちゃいましょう!
Well, let's just go!
次の曲は…
The next track is...
こちら!
Here!
ライオン
Lion
星を廻せ 世界のまん中で
Diving through the starlight,
くしゃみすれば どこかの森で 蝶が乱舞う
cut an arc through the heart of the world.
キミが守る ドアの鍵で ダラメダ
When you sneeze in a forest, butterflies flutter.
恥ずかしい物語 舐め合っても
Never fear to falter when protecting the key to the door,
ライオンは強い
through the shame that had left you stammering.
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
Let me live another day,
まだ生きてたくなる
let me see the future beckoning.
星座の導きで 今 見つめ合った
By the grace of every star above we met to reach the ending.
生き残りタイ 生き残りタイ
Let me live another day,
どうにくれたぎりに枯れてゆく
I don't know what more to say.
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまでは
In a glint it all was mended.
私眠らない
'Till the day that I can dance above in pride,
風はやがて 東へ向かうだろう
I swear I'll rise until the morning light.
The wind will eventually fly toward the east.
解き明かすこの星の ドアを襲う
The star's door, once deciphered, is attacked.
誘い水を 飲んだ 胸がつらい
Drinking the alluring water breaks my heart.
遠巻きな物語り かじり合う 骨の奥まで
A long-spun story, biting at each other to the bone.
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
Let me live another day,
まだ生きてたくなる
let me see the future beckoning.
星座の導きで 今 見つめ合った
By the grace of every star above we met to reach the ending.
生き残りタイ 生き残りタイ
Let me live another day,
どうにくれたぎりに枯れてゆく
I don't know what more to say.
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまでは 私眠らない
In a glint it all was mended.
何しに生まれたの
What were we born for?
何しにここにいる
What are we doing here?
生き残りたい 埋まらない傷 光恐れてた
I wanted to survive, fearing the light of unhealed wounds.
許された命が いま 惹かれあった
Now the forgiven lives are drawn together.
彷徨い果てて 君のとなりで ほてり鎮めたい
Wandering to the end, I want to calm my fever beside you.
本気のカラダ 見せ付けるまで 私眠らない
I won't sleep until I show you my true self.
生き残りたい 崖っぷちで 君を愛してる
I want to survive, loving you on the edge of a cliff.
目覚めたい命が いま 光あった
Now the lives that want to awaken shine.
狂気に変えて 祈り捧ぐよ 君を愛してる
Turning into madness, I offer my prayers, loving you.
星座の導きで...
Guided by the constellations...
生き残りたい まだ生きてたい 君を愛してる
I want to survive, I still want to live, loving you.
本気のココロ 見せ付けるまで 私眠らない
I won't sleep until I show you my true heart.
星間飛行 作詞：松本隆 作曲：菅野よう子
[Song: Seikan Hikou / Lyrics: Takashi Matsumoto / Music: Yoko Kanno]
水面が揺らぐ 風の輪が広がる
The water's surface ripples, expanding rings of wind.
触れ合った指先の発光電流
The luminous current of our touching fingertips.
見つめ合うだけで 孤独な加速度が
Just gazing at each other, our solitary acceleration
一瞬に砕け散る
shatters in an instant.
あなたが好きよ 透明な真珠のように
I love you, like a transparent pearl,
宙に浮く涙 悲劇だってかまわない
tears floating in space—tragedy doesn't matter.
あなたと生きたい
I want to live with you.
流星にまたがって
Riding on a shooting star,
あなたに急降下 ah ah
I'm diving down to you, ah ah.
濃朱の星空に 私たち花火みたい
In the deep crimson starlit sky, we're like fireworks,
心が光の矢を放つ
our hearts releasing arrows of light.
会話などなしに 内部に潜って
Without conversation, diving deep within,
考えが読み取れる 不思議な夜
a mysterious night where I can read your thoughts.
あなたの名 呪文みたいに 無限のリピート
Your name like a spell, on infinite repeat.
憎々しくて手の甲に 爪を立ててみる
Feeling resentful, I dig my nails into the back of my hand.
身体ごと通り抜け
Passing right through our bodies,
絵のように漂う uh uh
drifting like a painting, uh uh.
芥粒の生命でも 私たち瞬いてる
Even as specks of life, we are twinkling.
魂に銀河 雪崩れていく
Galaxies avalanche into our souls.
流星にまたがって あなたに急上昇 oh oh
Riding on a shooting star, soaring up to you, oh oh.
濃朱の星空に 私たち花火みたい
In the deep crimson starlit sky, we're like fireworks,
心が光の矢を放つ
our hearts releasing arrows of light.
あなたの呪文みたいに 無限の指先
Like a spell of yours, infinite fingertips
憎らしくて手の甲に 爪を立ててみる
Feeling bitter, I dig my nails into the back of my hand.
身体ごとすっぽり 絵のように彷徨う
Swallowed whole with our bodies, wandering like a painting,
けし粒の命でも 私たちまたたいてる
even as specks of life, we are twinkling.
新しい入り口が 並んでいく
New gateways are lining up,
あなたは急上昇 oh oh
you're soaring up, oh oh.
濃朱の星空に 私たち花火みたい
In the deep crimson starlit sky, we're like fireworks,
水面が揺らぐ 風の輪が広がる
Swaying surface, the ring of wind expands,
触れ合った指先の 青い電流
the blue electric current of our touching fingertips.
見つめあうだけで 孤独な加速度が
Just by looking at each other, the lonely acceleration
一瞬に砕け散る
shatters in an instant.
気付かぬうちに 同じでも
Even if we don't notice it,
新しい時代 また抱いている
we're embracing a new era once again.
魂に銀河 雪崩れてく
A galaxy avalanches into our souls,
a galaxy avalanches into our souls.
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
みんなどうだったかな？
How was everyone?
どうだったコメント見当たるんだ！
Let's see how the comments are looking!
コメント見てるよ！ パチパチパチありがとう！
We're reading the comments! Clap clap clap, thank you!
いっぱいありがとう！
Thank you so much!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
イェーイ！楽しいな！
Yay! So much fun!
めちゃ楽しいね！
Super fun!
みんなぎってきた！
Everyone's getting hyped!
テンション上がってきたぜ！上がってきたな！
Our tension is rising! It's going up!
あっち！あっち！
Over there! Over there!
あつあつだね！あっちよ！
It's super hot! Over there!
このあと二人でゆっくりしような。ゆっくりしような。
Let's relax together afterwards. Let's take it easy.
ライブが終わったらちょっと二人きりで、ゆっくりしようね今日。
Once the live is over, just the two of us will relax today.
あっちあっちになっちゃう。
It's getting all hot over there.
みんなの呟いてくれましたか？かなたライブ。
Did everyone tweet about it? Kanata Live.
あ、そうだそうだ。あ、すたぐ。
Ah, that's right. Ah, #suta-gu.
あ、りお先輩も見てる？よう見てる？りお先輩！
Ah, is Rio-senpai watching too? Are you watching? Rio-senpai!
ありがとう！りお先輩嬉しい！
Thank you! Rio-senpai, we're so happy!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
うれしいよ！
We're so happy!
どうかなみんな、お？
How is everyone, oh?
みんなぎってきた！おらおらこれね、かなたライブ。呟いていっぱい呟いてください！
Everyone's hyped! Come on, everyone, tweet a lot about Kanata Live!
お願いします！頑張って歌わせて頂きたいと思います！
Please do! We'll do our best to sing for you!
思います！スクショとかも！撮ってね！
We think! Take screenshots too! Please take them!
スクショもね。じゃあ近く寄るか。
Screenshots too. Let's get closer.
近く寄るか。
Let's get closer.
みんな、あのカメラここ？ちょっと恥ずかしいな。テレテレ。
Everyone, um, is the camera here? This is a little embarrassing. Shy shy.
恥ずかしいな。くっついちゃった。くっついちゃったよ。
So embarrassing. We bumped into each other. We bumped into each other.
かなたの方が背が高い。
Kanata is taller.
なんかちょっと今年は僕、あのちょっとズルス、あ、ずっこにゃんじゃねえの？ズルスしてるんですよねって。
Today I'm kind of... cheating, ah, isn't that cheating? I'm cheating.
あ、あ、なんか、ほら、あ、なんか高くない？それ。
Ah, ah, somehow, look, ah, isn't it tall? That.
どうかな？僕ちょっとスパダリ感出てる？求め、求めいいよ。
What do you think? Do I give off a super darlin' vibe? You can ask for it.
僕の胸で泣いてもいいよ。
You can cry on my chest.
胸ね、じゃあね。
Your chest, huh, sure.
あるだろうが！あるだろうが胸は！
Of course there is! Of course I have a chest!
あるだろう大きいのが！胸ね、じゃあ。こんな感じですかね？
Of course a big one exists! A chest, huh. Is this how it is?
うん、みんなこのまま盛り上がっていけるかな？まだまだ歌うよ！イェーイ！
Yep, can everyone keep getting hyped like this? We're still gonna sing! Yay!
それでは次の曲、どうぞ！だった。
And now, for the next song, here you go! That was it.
UFO
手を合わせて見つめるだけで
Simply by putting our hands together and gazing,
愛し合える話もできる
we can talk about loving each other.
くちづけするより甘くささやきより強く
Sweeter than a kiss, stronger than a whisper,
私の心を揺さぶるあなた
you shake my heart.
迷いわずに思っただけで
Just by thinking without hesitation,
すぐあなたにわかってしまう
you understand right away.
眠りたくなったらベッド
If you want to sleep, a bed,
次から次へとさし出すあなた
you offer one thing after another.
信じられないことばかりあるの
There are only unbelievable things happening,
もしからしたらもしからしたら宇宙の歌手だわ
perhaps, perhaps you're a cosmic singer!
それでもいいわ 近頃少し
Even so, it's fine. Lately, just a bit...
地球の赤道に 飽きたところよ
I'm getting kind of tired of Earth's equator.
ああ
Ah...
それでも私は 確かめたいわ
Even so, I want to make sure.
その凄さを 一度は見たい
I want to see that amazing sight at least once.
鏡に写してみたり
Trying to reflect it in a mirror,
光をあててもみたり
or shining a light on it,
それでもあなたは 普通のあなた
even so, you are just an ordinary you.
ああ 突然 オレンジ色の
Ah, suddenly an orange-colored...
光が私を包み
light envelops me,
夢見る気持ちにさせて どこかへさらってゆくわ
making me feel like I'm dreaming, carrying me off somewhere.
やっぱりそんなの 素敵なあなた
As expected, such a wonderful you...
信じられないことでしょうけれど
It might be unbelievable, but...
嘘じゃないの 嘘じゃないの 本当のことよ
It's no lie, it's no lie, it's the truth!
それでもいいわ 近頃少し
Even so, it's fine. Lately, just a bit...
地球の赤道に 飽きたところよ
I'm getting kind of tired of Earth's equator.
ああ
Ah...
ああ、びっくりした。
Ah, that scared me.
みんな！
Everyone!
UFOね
UFOs, right?
UFO、途中のUFOが言えなかったんだけど
UFO—I couldn't say UFO in the middle.
言えなかったね。
You couldn't say it.
言えなかったね。あれ？
You couldn't say it. Huh?
あれ、わためはなんか準備？
Huh, Watame, did you prepare something?
ちょっと、行ってくるね。
Hold on, I'm going over there.
どこ行くの？
Where are you going?
ごめんね、ちょっと。
Sorry, just a second.
つないでてよ。
Keep holding the conversation!
UFO！
UFO!
つないで！UFOの後一人ぼっちにしないでよ！
Keep it going! Don't leave me all alone after UFO!
頑張るよ！
I'll do my best!
なんて、映されそう！
Oh gosh, I'm gonna get projected!
あ、待って、どこ行くの？ UFOに…
Ah, wait, where are you going? To the UFO...
UFOをやめて！
Stop with the UFO!
あ、あれ？ わため…
Huh? Watame...
ポピ、ポピポピ、あれなんか、天の声となってしまった、わためがみんな、みんな言ってしまうんだ、わためポピポピポプル。
Popi, popipopi... somehow Watame became the voice from above, and everyone's saying it... Watame popipopipopuru.
ああ、行っちゃったよ。みんなどうでした？ 紹介、UFOは…
Ah, she went away. How was everyone? Introducing UFO...
えっと、これはですね、踊るの、踊る予定じゃなかったんだけど、ちょっと直前に、え、ちょっとぐらいやっぱり踊りたいよねって話をね、したんですよね。
Um, so, we weren't planning on dancing to this, but right before, we talked about how we'd still love to dance to it a little bit.
あの、マリンちゃんところね先輩がUFO踊ってたでしょ？だからさ、
You know, Marine-chan and Korone-senpai danced to UFO, right? So,
僕もさ、あの全くUFO知らなくて、で一生懸命ちょっとね、ダンスを覚えようとしたんだけど時間足りず、あ、時間足りずUFOも言えず、もしけな、ごめんねみんな。
I didn't know UFO at all either, and I tried desperately to learn the dance, but I ran out of time, couldn't even say UFO, sorry everyone.
その直前で、わためは、わためはちょっとダンスしてたのだけ？
Right before that, Watame—was Watame dancing a little bit?
え？
Eh?
わためはダンスしてたんだよね、ちょっと。
Watame was dancing a bit, right?
うん、ちょっと見てきたよ。
Yeah, I went and took a look.
ちょっと踊る気だったよ、わため。
Watame was actually in the mood to dance a bit.
うん。
Yeah.
見てきた、予定はね、あ、て、予定はなかったけどね、わためを踊る気だった。UFOをちょっとね。
I went and checked. We didn't plan on it, but Watame was in the mood to dance. To do UFO a bit.
やっぱUFO出したがね、UFO！
She really wanted to put out UFO, UFO!
はい、ということでね、皆さんどうでしょうか？楽しんでいただけておるでしょうか？
Alright, so everyone, how was it? Did you enjoy it?
まだまだね、かなたライブ続いていきますので、よろしければこちらも引き続きもよろしくお願いします。
Kanata Live will still continue, so if you'd like, please keep supporting this stream as well.
あ、わため、なんかもう終わった？準備が終わったみたいななので、
Ah, Watame, did it already end? It seems like preparations are finished, so...
あ、降りてきたね。
Ah, she came back down.
それでは、わためで
And now, with Watame...
空色デイズ。
"Sorairo Days".
君は聴こえる? 僕のこの声が
Can you hear it? This voice of mine
闇に虚しく 吸い込まれた
was sucked emptily into darkness.
もしもし世界が 意味を持つなら こんな気持ちも無駄ではない
If the world has meaning, then even these feelings aren't in vain.
憧れに押し潰されて
Crushed by yearning...
諦めてたんだ
I had given up.
果てしない空の色も知らないで
Without even knowing the color of the endless sky,
走り出した
I started running.
想いが今でも この胸を確実に叩いているから
My feelings even now are firmly beating against my heart,
今日の僕が その先に続く
So the me of today will continue beyond that
僕らなりの明日を築いていく
And build our own tomorrow.
答えはそう いつもここにある
The answer, yes, is always right here.
過ぎた季節を嘆く暇はない
There's no time to lament passing seasons,
二度と迷ってしまわぬように
So I won't ever lose my way again.
数えきれない ほんのささやかな そんな後悔 抱えたまま
With countless, tiny regrets still held in my arms,
その背中だけ追いかけて ここまで来たんだ
Chasing only that back, I've come this far.
探していた 僕だけにできること
Searching for what only I can do,
あの日くれた言葉が 今でも この胸に確実に届いているから
Those words you gave me that day are still reaching my heart reliably.
昨日よりも今日の僕は 僕の生まれてきたわけに気付いていく
Today more than yesterday, I realize the reason I was born.
答えはそう いつもここにある
The answer, yes, is always right here.
すべてが丸で当たり前みたいだ
It was as if everything was completely natural,
遠い日々は まだ終わらない そして
Our precious days haven't ended yet, and then...
走り出した
I started running,
想いが今でも この胸を確実に叩いているから
Because my feelings even now are beating against my chest.
今日の僕が その先に続く
The me of today will continue beyond that,
僕らなりの明日を築いていく
Building our own tomorrow.
答えはそう いつもここにある
The answer, yes, is always right here.
その通りでしょだから
That's right, isn't it?
ふぅ、どうでしたか？
Phew, how was it?
空色デイズでした！
That was "Sorairo Days"!
どうでしたか？どうでしたか？
How was it? How was it?
楽しかったですか？めちゃ気持ちよかったな！
Did you have fun? It felt amazing!
聞いてたかかなた！ あれ？き、聞いてたよ。
Were you listening, Kanata? Huh? I, I was listening.
どこで聞いてたんだ。
Where were you listening?
私ね、ぼく、ごめん、実家帰ったわ。
Well, I, sorry, I went back to my parents' house.
なんで帰ったの！ ごめん、ちょっと展開から取り残されております。
Why'd you go back?! Sorry, I'm a bit left behind by the plot.
これこそ天の声なんですけど、ごめん。
This is supposed to be the voice from heaven, but sorry.
これが真の天の声。
This is the true voice from heaven.
まだちょっと準備中。準備中？ということは？
We're still kind of in preparation. Preparation? That means...
何かが… ちょっと準備して歩いてること？
Something is... walking while getting ready?
かなた、何かがあるってこと？ 何よ？
Kanata, does that mean something's happening? What is it?
かなたに何かがあるってこと！
Something's happening to Kanata!
わあ、何があるのかな？
Wow, I wonder what it is?
めちゃ楽しみだね！ え？
I'm super looking forward to it! Huh?
え？ほら、シャープかなたわライブで、ね？お願いします。
Eh? Look, #KanataLive, right? Please.
次と、楽しみだね！ え？次かなたさん？
Next, I'm looking forward to it! Eh? Next is Kanata-san?
え？何待っているの？ もうすぐか？
Eh? What are you waiting for? Coming soon?
え？ なんてね？ ツイートしてもらってもいいんですよ。
Eh? Just kidding. You can tweet about it too, you know.
そして、あのビリビリでも今同時配信をしているので、かなたのチャンネルですね！
And also, we're currently simulcasting on Bilibili too, so on Kanata's channel!
ええ？ 大丈夫か？
Eh? Is it alright?
今はええとかなたのチャンネルでやらせていただいております。
Right now, um, we're doing this on Kanata's channel.
見てくれてるのぜ。ぴりぴりのみんな、よろしくね。
Thanks for watching. Everyone at Piripiri, nice to meet you.
ありがとね、ぴりぴりのみんなも。
Thank you, everyone at Piripiri too.
ね、見てくれてありがとう。
Hey, thank you for watching.
せぇーの！ わあ、あいーに！ イエーイ！ やー！
Ready, go! Wow, ai-ni! Yay! Yeah!
「そうなんだ」って。あ、あ、ねえ、やばいやばい、「そうなんだしって」っていうコメントがあるぞ。
"Is that so?" Ah, ah, hey, yaba yaba. There's a comment saying "Is that so?".
あ、わき、あ、わきわきわきわき。わき？ すかすか、ちょっとわきわき見せ、ちょっとわきを今度ちゃんと見せて、いざだけ
Ah, armpit, ah, armpit armpit armpit. Armpit? Sparse, show armpits a bit... show your armpits properly next time...
あ、うわ！ やばい！ でわ、やばい。テンションが！ やばい、爆発してしまう。
Ah, whoa! Yaba! Wow, yaba. My tension! Yaba, it's gonna explode.
まだ、準備。
Not ready yet.
まだ、まだ？
Not yet, not yet?
まだ。
Not yet.
もう繋げないよ。
I can't connect anymore.
繋いで、また、もっと繋いで。繋いだげようか。
Connect, again, connect more. Shall I connect?
うん、繋いで。
Yeah, connect.
ええ、もう準備できたの？
Eh, are you ready already?
できた。
Done.
できたんかい！
You're done already?!
できた。
Done.
では、聞いてください。あまねかなたで「夜に駆ける」。
Now then, please listen. "Yoru ni Kakeru" by Amane Kanata.
沈むように溶けていくように
It's like we're sinking, it's like we're melting,
二人だけの空が広がる夜に
on that night where the sky stretched endlessly, just for the two of us.
「さよなら」だけだった
It was only a simple "goodbye,"
その一言で全てが分かった
but it was all I needed to understand.
日が沈み出した空と君の姿
The sinking sun and your figure
フェンス越しに重なっていた
were overlapping beyond the fence.
初めて会った日から
Ever since the first day we met,
僕の心の全てを奪った
you stole all of my heart.
どこか儚い空気を纏う君は
Wrapped in some sort of fragile air,
寂しい目をしていたんだ
you had a lonely gaze.
いつだってチックタックと鳴る世界で何度だってさ
Again and again in the world always ringing with "tick-tocks",
触れる心無い言葉うるさい声に涙が零れそうでも
Even if the tears seem about to spill over touching thoughtless words and irritating voices,
ありきたりな喜びきっと二人なら見つけられる
As long as we're together, I'm sure we can find an ordinary happiness.
騒がしい日々に笑えない君に思い付く限り眩しい明日を
In the troubling days, for the never-smiling you, I give my utmost wishes for a dazzling tomorrow.
明けない夜に落ちていく前に僕の手を掴んでほんで
Before we fall in the never-ending night, come and take my hand.
忘れてしまいたくて閉じ込めた日々も
Even the days where you shut yourself away, wanting to forget,
抱きしめた温もりで溶かすから
I'll melt with the warmth of my embrace,
怖くないよいつか日が昇るまで二人でいよう
So don't be afraid. Until the sun rises again someday, let's be together.
君にしか見えない
I hate it when you stare at
何かを見つめる君が嫌いだ
the things only you can see.
見惚れているかのような恋するようなそんな顔が嫌いだ
Like you're captivated by it, or you're in love—I hate that expression.
信じてたいけど信じられないことそんなのどうしたってきっと
The things I want to believe but I can't... No matter what I do,
これからだっていくつもあって
they'll pop up again and again from now on.
そのたんび怒って泣いていくの
And every time I'll get angry and cry.
それでもきっといつかはきっと僕らはきっと分かり合えるさ
Even so, someday we'll surely, we'll understand each other; I believe that.
もう嫌だって疲れたんだってがむしゃらに差し伸べた僕の手を振り払う君
"I don't want this, I'm tired of it," I frantically reach for your hand, but you push my hands away.
もう嫌だって疲れたよなんて本当は僕も言いたいんだ
"I don't want this, I'm tired of it," to tell the truth, I want to say that too.
騒がしい日々に何度だってさ君のために用意した言葉どれも届かない
In the world ringing with "tick-tocks," again and again, none of the words I've prepared for you reach you.
「終わりにするんだ」なんてさ釣られて言葉にした時君は初めて笑った
"I want to end it all," when I went along and said that, you smiled for the first time.
騒がしい日々に笑えなくなっていた僕の目に映る君は綺麗だ
In the troubling days, I became unable to smile—you are truly beautiful in my eyes.
明けない夜に溢れた涙も君の笑顔に溶けていく
The spilled-over tears in the never-ending night all dissolve into your smile.
変わらない日に泣いていた僕を君は優しく終わりへと誘う
In the never-changing days when I cried, you gently tempt me towards the end.
沈むように溶けていくように染み付いた霧が晴れる
It's like we're sinking, it's like we're melting, the indelibly stained fog dissipates.
沈むように 溶けていくように
Just like I'm about to sink, just like I'm about to melt
二人だけの空が広がる夜に
Only the two of us at night in the vast sky stretching out
その一言で 全てが分かった
With just that one word, I understood everything
日が沈み出した空と君の姿
The sky where the sun began to set and your figure
フェンス越しに重なっていた
Overlapping across the fence
初めて会った日から
From the day we first met
僕の心の全てを奪った
You stole away everything inside my heart
どこか儚い空気を纏う君は
Somewhere, you wearing a fleeting atmosphere
寂しい目をしていたんだ
Had such a lonely look in your eyes
はい、皆さんどうでしたでしょうか。
Yes, everyone, how was it?
夜に駆ける歌わせていただきました。
I got to sing "Yoru ni Kakeru".
よっしゃ、みんなどうだったかな。ありがと！パチパチありがと！
Alright, I wonder how it was for everyone. Thank you! Clap clap, thank you!
ええ、カナタライブもね、ライブ終盤の方になってまいりました。
Um, the Kanata Live is also reaching its final stage.
みんなどうだったかな。今日楽しんでくれているかな。
I wonder how it was for everyone. Are you enjoying today?
嬉しいな。あのね、結構前に一緒にライブしたいねって3Dでライブしたいねって
I'm so happy. You know, quite a while ago, we talked about wanting to live together in 3D...
話をしておりまして、
and had discussions about it,
で、その時からやっとね、カナタ念願の今日、念願のデュエットお互い本当にね、今日楽しみにしておりました。
and ever since then, today, Kanata's long-cherished duet—we've both truly been looking forward to today.
かなただけに、かなた！
"Only to Kanata, Kanata!"
あれ？今天の声から聞こえたぞ？
Huh? I just heard the voice of heaven?
かなただけに、かなた！かなた、あまね、かなた！
"Only to Kanata, Kanata! Kanata, Amane, Kanata!"
かなえました！夢かなったね！
"It came true! Your dream came true, right?"
そう、かなたがね、声をかけてくれてね、一緒にやろうよって、で、今回実現したんですよ！
"That's right, Kanata called out to me and said let's do it together, and this time it came true!"
なんですよう！ありがとうみんな！ありがとう！
"That's right! Thank you everyone! Thank you!"
そうなんです。すごいね楽しみにしてて、一緒にねずっと歌いたいねと言っていたんだけどさ、ねえ？
"That's right. I was really looking forward to it, and we kept saying we wanted to sing together all the time, right?"
あ、ね、あ、あ、あ、よし、そんな感じでね、
"Ah, yeah, ah, ah, ah, alright, with that said,"
どうでしょうか次、綿芽の用意できているかな。
"how about the next one? Is Watame ready?"
綿芽準備しているかな、これ。ちょっと待ってな。
"Is Watame preparing this? Wait a minute."
準備中？まだ、まだ準備中。
"In preparation? Still, still in preparation."
あ、まだちょっと着替えてる。
"Ah, still changing clothes."
あ、痒いとこか。あ、痒いとこ。
"Ah, the itchy spot. Ah, the itchy spot."
意外ではない、痒いらしい。ちゃんとね、ちゃんと書いてね。
"Not unexpected, seems it's itchy. Make sure you scratch properly."
ぽりぽりぽりぽり。いいぞ、いいぞ、いいぞ、いいぞって。
"Scratch scratch scratch scratch. Good, good, good, good."
甘噛み聞こえてくる。あ、急にね、あのね、そう、甘噛みをしたりするとすごく怒られてしまうから。
"Hearing sweet nibbles. Ah, suddenly, you know, if you do sweet nibbles like that, you get scolded a lot."
そう、怒りたいところなんだけどね、すごくね。そうなの、みんなどうかな。
"That's the part I want to get scolded for, you know, very much. That's right, how is everyone?"
普段献血とかムしてるような人に見えねえ？え、本当？
"Don't you look like someone who normally donates blood? Eh, really?"
一生懸命頑張りました。いや、本当にね、
"I tried my best. Man, truly,"
体力がなくて不安もたくさんあったけど、綿芽と一緒に歌うのはとても楽しくって。
"I didn't have much stamina and had a lot of anxiety, but singing together with Watame was so much fun."
んね！んね！あ、準備できたっぽいかも！
"Right! Right! Ah, it looks like preparations are done!"
枠なくなった！あ、枠なくなったじゃん！よく書いた、よく書いた！
"The frame is gone! Ah, the frame is gone! Good job, good job!"
よく書いた！よく書いた！よく書いた！よし！
"Good job! Good job! Good job! Alright!"
それでは、次の曲行きますか！行きますか！はいよ！
"Well then, shall we go to the next song? Shall we go? Alright!"
せーの、紅蓮華！
"Ready, go, Gurenge!"
強くなれる理由を知った
I got to know the reason I could get strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and advance
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Intoxicated by the muddy lantern light
こわばる心震える手は
My heart is frozen, my trembling hand
掴みたいものがある それだけさ
There is something I want to attain, that's all
夜の匂いに空睨んでも 変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ それだけさ
Even if I stare into the night sky, the only thing I can change is myself, that's all
強くなれる理由を知った 僕を連れて進め
I got to know the reason I could get strong, take me with you and advance
どうしたって!
No matter what!
消せない夢も 止まれない今も
The unforgettable dreams and the unstoppable now
誰かのために強くなれるなら ありがとう 悲しみよ
If I'm able to get strong for someone, thank you, oh sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Overwhelmed by the world, I got to know what it means to lose
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ! 運命を照らして
Oh crimson lotus, bloom! Illuminate my destiny
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The thunderous boom pierced my ears
惑う心 優しさだけじゃ守れないものがある
My heart is at a loss, there are things I cannot protect with only kindness
わかっているけど
I know that, but
水面下で絡まる善悪 透けて見える偽善に天罰
Under the surface, good and evil are entangled, divine punishment to the obvious hypocrisy
(Tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me... I don't need you!)
逸材の花より 挑戦し続け咲いた一輪が美しい
The flower who kept on trying to bloom is more beautiful than the natural prodigy
乱暴に敷き詰められた トゲだらけの道も
Because the road that's filled with dangerous thorns, too
本気の僕だけに現れるから 乗り越えてみせるよ
will only reveal itself when I'm resolute, I will overcome it
強くなれる理由を知った
I got to know the reason I could get strong.
僕を連れて 進め
Take me with you and advance!
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Intoxicated by the muddy lantern light,
こわばる心 震える手は
my heart is frozen.
掴みたいものがある
There is something my trembling hand wants to attain.
変っていけるのは自分自身だけ
The only thing I can change is myself.
強くなれる理由を知った
I got to know the reason I could get strong.
僕を連れて 進め
Take me with you and advance!
どうしたって消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what the unforgettable dreams and the unstoppable now,
誰かのために強くなれるなら
if I'm able to get strong for someone,
ありがとう 悲しみよ
thank you, oh sadness!
世界に打ちのめされて
Overwhelmed by the world,
負ける意味を知った
I got to know what it means to protect.
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ 運命を照らして
Oh crimson lotus, bloom! Illuminate my destiny!
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The thunderous boom pierced my ears,
戸惑う心優しいだけじゃ
my heart is at a loss.
守れないものがある
There are things I cannot protect with only kindness.
わかってるけど
I know that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Under the surface, good and evil are entangled.
透けて見える偽善に天罰
Divine punishment to the obvious hypocrisy!
Tell me why tell me why tell me why tell me
I don't need you
逸材の花より 挑戦し続け咲いた一輪が美しい
The flower who kept on trying to bloom is more beautiful than the natural prodigy.
乱暴に敷き詰められた トゲだらけの道も
Because the road that's filled with dangerous thorns, too,
本気の僕だけに現れるから
will only reveal itself when I'm resolute.
乗り越えてみせるよ
I will overcome it!
簡単に片付けられた 守れなかった夢も
No matter what the unforgettable dreams and the unstoppable now,
紅蓮的心臓に根を生やす
if I'm able to get strong for someone,
この血に宿っている
thank you, oh sadness!
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ 運命を照らして
Oh crimson lotus, bloom! Illuminate my destiny!
運命を照らして
Illuminate my destiny!
さあ眠眠打破 昼夜逆転 VOXアンプ三十ワット
So, it's time to wake up, turn the vox 30 watts up!
テレキャスター背負ったサブカルボーイが
A telecaster worn by a suburban boy,
バンド仲間にやっほー
jammin' away with his garage band.
アルバイトはネクラモード
Working part-time is so emo,
対バンにはATフィールド
and his rivals crush his ego.
人見知り宣言で逃げる気か boy
Sick and tired of your excuses, "anti-social" boy!
ゆーて お坊ちゃんお嬢ちゃん
All these outsiders put money where their mouth is,
お金も才能も なまじっかあるだけ厄介でやんす
threatening society and losers like me!
boys be ambitious... like this old man
長い前髪 君誰の信者 信者 信者
Hey there godforsaken dude, so tell me who you worship!
勘違いすんな 教祖はオマエだ
Hell don't get me wrong because the guru lies in you!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Rockin' rockin' roll, rockin' rockin' roll!
かき鳴らすエレクトリックギターは
Make love with your electric guitar!
don't stop! don't stop!
さあ君の全てを 曝け出してみせろよ
So, are you giving up? Better show me what you've got!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Rockin' rockin' roll, rockin' rockin' roll!
さあ日進月歩
So, take a step up!
いい曲書いてる? 動画増えてる?
New song in the brew? Is it buzzing too?
「知名度あるけど 人気はそんなにないから
"Your name is game, but your fame is lame
色々大変ですね。」
so I feel really bad for you."
はっきり言うなよ 匿名アイコン
Hate to break the news to ya, anonymous icon!
はっきり見せない 実写のアイコン
Hate to break the news to ya, real-life icon!
いい齢こいて 自意識まだ boy
They say it's time to act your age, your heart is still a boy!
ぶっちぎりどんだけ賢くあざとくやったって
No matter how clever you attempt to endeavor,
10年後にメイクは落ちてんだろ
like it or not, in ten years, your colors will show!
boys be ambitious... like this old man
生き抜くためだ キメろ take a selfie
Your instagram is on the line, it's time to take a selfie!
selfie selfie
死ぬんじゃねぇぞ お互いにな!
I'll see you on the other side, if only we survive!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Rockin' rockin' roll, rockin' rockin' roll!
薄っぺらいラブソングでもいい
Just give me another cheesy love song!
don't stop! don't stop!
さあ目の前のあの子を 撃ち抜いてみせろよ
So, are you giving up? Better show me what you've got!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Rockin' rockin' roll, rockin' rockin' roll!
お茶を濁してちゃ満足できない
Blinded by perfection, but can't get no satisfaction!
スタジオに運ばれたスロートコートは
All these pricey goods and gizmos they try to seduce me with...
安心不安シンプレッシャーでいっぱい
Sanity? Insanity? The pressure is crushing!
「実は昨日から風邪で声が出ません」
"Hate to break the news, but my voice died, the show is off tonight!"
は? は? は? は?
Huh? Say what? No way! Shut up!
寝言は寝て言え ベイビー
Say wisecracks and keep dreaming, baby!
死ぬんじゃねぇぞ お互いにな!
I'll see you on the other side, if only we survive!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Rockin' rockin' roll, rockin' rockin' roll!
かき鳴らすエレクトリックギターは
Make love with your electric guitar!
寝言は寝て言え
Sleep-talk in your sleep,
ベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビーベイビー
baby, baby, baby, baby, baby!
死ぬんじゃねぇぞ お互いにな!
Don't you dare die on me, let's survive together!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Roki-roki rock and roll,
かき鳴らす エレクトリックギターは
strumming that electric guitar—
don't stop! don't stop! さぁ君の全てを
don't stop! don't stop! Come on, show me everything!
さらけ出してみせろよ
Show me everything you've got!
ロキロキのロックンロックンロール
Roki-roki rock and roll,
死ぬんじゃねぇぞ お互いにな!
Don't you dare die on me, let's survive together!
yeah! I! I! I! I! I! I!
yeah! I! I! I! I!
なんかさっきの今
That was just...
けっつすべった
My hip totally slipped!
え？
Huh?
けっつすべった
My hip slipped!
はい、みんな
Alright everyone,
どうだったでしょうか、「ロキ」！
how was it? "Roki"!
ロキ！
Roki!
と、ロキをね、歌わせていただきました。
We got to sing Roki together!
どうだったでしょう、が
How was—
楽しかったね！
That was so fun!
楽しかったー！めちゃ楽しかった！
It was so fun! So much fun!
楽しすぎてもう、汗だくよ。
It was so fun I'm all sweaty.
やっぱり。
Totally.
もうね、本当に、みんなには見えない心の汗をかいている、心もボウボウに燃えているからね。
We're sweating invisible heart-sweat, our hearts are blazing!
ロキをかった、ありがとう！
We got through Roki, thank you!
ありがとう！いぇーい！
Thank you! Yay!
スクショも撮ってくれたりとかしてる、みんな。
Everyone's taking screenshots, right?
スクショは、撮る？ え、あ、なんか、スクショポーズ撮る？スクショタイム、なかったもんね。そうなんだよね、なかったね。
Did you take screenshots? Oh, should we do a screenshot pose? There was no screenshot time. Yeah, there wasn't.
どう？あ、恥ずかしい？みんな見てるよ。いいじゃない。みんな見てる。
How's this? Ah, embarrassing? Everyone's watching. It's fine. Everyone's watching.
わため、わため、髪絡まっちゃった。ごめんね、髪絡まっちゃった。ちょっと絡まっちゃった。
Watame, Watame, your hair got tangled. Sorry, your hair got tangled. It got tangled.
ちょっと絡まっちゃった。
It got a bit tangled.
わための怪我絡まっちゃった。ちょっと絡みすぎちゃった。
Our hair got tangled. It got way too tangled.
お手ては、手がちょっともさもさなもんで、あの、後でね、一緒に溶かそうね。ありがとう！
Our hands are a bit clumsy, let's untangle it together later. Thank you!
あ、撮ってくれたみんな、ありがとう！
Ah, everyone who took photos, thank you!
とりあえずだな…
Anyway...
どーーまん！はい、どーーまん！
Do-man! Yes, do-man!
あ、怒られる！
Ah, we'll get scolded!
あ、いけないんだ、いけないんだ、いけないんだ！
Ah, we can't do that, we can't do that!
先生に怒られる。先生はいないな。でもほら、あのブラックホールだし。
The teacher will scold us. There's no teacher. But hey, that's a black hole!
おとめは？ おとめは？ 怒られたくないよ。おいとめも怒られたくないよ。
What about Otome? I don't want to get scolded. I don't want Otime to get scolded either.
いいえ！かわいい！ど忘れ！やばいよ、やばいよ！やりたいよ！
No! Cute! Forgot! This is bad, this is bad! I want to do it!
え、それではですね、え、そろそろ、な、なんで空色デイズを選んだの？
Um, well then, um, why did you choose "Sorairo Days"?
やっぱね、天元突破したかったんだよね。
Well, you know, I wanted to break through the heavens.
わかるわかる、わかる！わかっちまった、わかっちまった！そう、わかっちまった！
I know, I know! I get it! Yes, I got it!
本当いい曲だし、ね、わためすごいよかった！
It's such a great song, and Watame, you were so good!
よかった！ね、いぇい！いぇい！いぇい！いぇい！ってやってたからね。
It was great! We were going "Yay! Yay! Yay!" like that.
花息よ。
Breathing heavily.
聞こえてたかもしれない。
People might have heard it.
あなたはなんで夜にかけたの？僕はね、夜にかけるという曲を結構最近知ったんだけど、
Why did you choose "Yoru ni Kakeru", Watame? I recently learned about it,
とっても素敵な曲だなと思って、歌詞とかもね、あの、もともと小説からあの曲をね、書き起こしているみたいなんだけどさ、素敵なだなと思ってPV、MVまですごい綺麗で…
and I thought it was such a wonderful song, with lyrics based on a novel, and even the PV and MV are so beautiful...
ない？うー、ふふ、ふふふ、ね。
Right? Um, hehe, hehehe, you know.
オッケー、オッケー、ピーピーむない、15か。ふふ。
Okay, okay... 15th? Hehe.
初めての、歌ってみた動画を投稿します！やー、いぇー！
We're releasing our first cover song video! Yay, yeah!
こちら！chocolate box！いぇーい！いぇーい！
Here it is! Chocolate Box! Yay! Yay!
こんな感じの曲じゃない、いぇー、いぇー！
It's not really that kind of song, yeah, yeah!
カッコいい、この曲はめちゃめちゃカッコいい、可愛い曲ですね。
It's cool, this song is super cool and cute.
こっちの方が可愛い曲でしてね。
This one is more of a cute song, you see.
ベリーキュート。そう、ベリーキュート。
Very cute. Yes, very cute.
カナタあんどわため、イズカップル。これカップルになってる、この曲では。
Kanata and Watame are a couple in this song.
あの曲ではね。あ、いつでも、いつでもカップルだよ。
In that song. Ah, anytime, we're always a couple.
いつでもカップルだよ。この後も一緒に見ようね。みんなも一緒に見ようね。動画見ようね。
Always a couple. Let's watch together after this too.
ということで、それではみんな、残念ながら、アンコールありがとうございました！
So, everyone, unfortunately... Thank you for the encore!
あ、アンコールありがとうございます！そう、アンコールにしましょう。
Ah, thank you for the encore! Yes, let's do an encore.
はい、みんな盛り上がって、最後もいっぱい盛り上がって！行けるかー！？
Yes, everyone get hyped, get super hyped to the end! Can you do it?!
それじゃあ、行くぞー！せーのっ！SKILL！
Well then, here we go! Ready, set! SKILL!
おーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおー
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
お前の勇気 昂る時
When your bravery peaks,
運命のドア 開かれる！
the door of fate will be opened!
それは夜明けか 永久の闇か
Will that be dawn, or eternal darkness,
鋼の拳に問え！
ask the fist of steel!
遙かな大宇宙に 光の矢を放つんだ！
Launch an arrow of light into the distant cosmos!
I can fly! (hey!)
You can fly!? (hey!)
We can fly! (hey!)
“もっともっと”
More and more!
Skill my heart!
銀河の果てまで 熱い夢を燃やせ
To the edge of the galaxy, burn your passionate dreams!
All I can do!
Skill my soul!
魂を呼び覚ませ！
Cry awake your soul!
時代が俺を導く限り 無敵さ…… (ALL RIGHT!!)
As long as the era guides me, I am invincible! (ALL RIGHT!!)
おーおーおーおーおーおーおーおー
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
天を切り裂く 巨大な剣
The great sword that cuts through heavens,
奇跡の力 蘇る！
the power of miracles is reborn!
愛する友よ 熱い胸で 鋼のビートに問え！
My loving friend, listen to the steel beat in your chest!
新たな伝説を 今 この手で刻むんだ！
Now, carve a new legend with these hands!
I can fly! (hey!)
You can fly!? (hey!)
We can fly! (hey!)
“もっともっと”
More and more!
Skill my heart!
次元の彼方に 物語を飛ばせ
To the depth of the dimension, launch the story!
I'll never die!
Skill my soul!
何度でも立ち上がれ！
Stand up again and again!
未来が俺を導く限り 不死身さ……
As long as the future guides me, I am immortal!
おーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおーおー
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
I can fly! (hey!)
You can fly!? (hey!)
We can fly! (hey!)
遥かなる おもいそらに
Into the distant skies of my thoughts...
光の絵を 放たんだ
unleashing a painting of light...
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!
まんたん まんたん まんたん まんたん まんたん まんたん
Full tank, full tank, full tank, full tank!
キミマイハート 銀河の果てまで
You're my heart, to the edge of the galaxy,
熱い夢を 燃やせ
burn your passionate dreams
光輝いて！
and shine bright!
キミマイハート 楽しみを呼び覚まして
You're my heart, awakening the joy within,
願いが我を導く限り 無敵さ
as long as my wish guides me, I'm invincible!
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!
You get a fight! Hey!
We get a fight! Hey!
もっともっと！
More, more!